brownsfashion.com 2018-09-26

# Help & Contact Us | Browns Fashion

##### Say Hello!

We want to be there for you whenever you need us. Here’s how you can get in touch.

**United Kingdom - Customer Care**  
Phone: +44 (0) 203 962 1241  
Monday to Sunday: 9am - 6pm (GMT)  
English only

**United States - Customer Care**  
Phone: +1 (347) 983 6574  
Monday to Friday: 9am - 6pm (PST)  
English only

**Email**  
_[customercare@brownsfashion.com](mailto:customercare@brownsfashion.com)_  
Monday to Friday: 9am - 2am (GMT)  
Saturday to Sunday: 9am - 6pm (GMT)

**Browns  Mayfair**

23-27 South Molton Street  
London W1K 5RD

Womenswear

Phone: +44 (0) 20 7514 0016  
Email: _[womenswear@brownsfashion.com](mailto:womenswear@brownsfashion.com)_

Menswear

Phone: +44 (0) 20 7514 0038  
Email:  _[mens@brownsfashion.com](mailto:mens@brownsfashion.com)_  

**Browns East**

21 Club Row  
London E2 7EY

Phone: +44 (0) 20 7729 2666  
Email: _[brownseast@brownsfashion.com](mailto:brownseast@brownsfashion.com)_

**Other Enquiries**

**Can’t find what you’re looking for?**

_[Tweet Us](https://twitter.com/BrownsFashion)  
[Ask Us On Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/brownsfashion/)_

##### Find. Order. Pay. Repeat.

Once you’ve dipped into our 

_designer categories_

via the dropdown navigation (from dresses and denim to Gucci and Saint Laurent) no doubt you’ll have your eye on at least a couple of items.

If you’ve found something you’d like to purchase, select your size (if you need a little extra guidance peruse the ‘Size & fit’ on the product page) and then click ‘Add To Bag’.

Now you can decide whether it’s time to give your credit card more of a workout or go directly to your ‘[Bag](https://www.brownsfashion.com/commerce/bag)’ to review and complete your order.

New customers will be required to 

_[create an account](https://www.brownsfashion.com/account/myaccount)_

with Browns before their order can be processed (returning customers, you know the drill), and always do a final check on your order before payment.

Once the order has been placed, we will email may you shortly after to confirm receipt of the order before we initiate our validation process.

Finally, if everything checks out you’ll have your new things in no time.

If you have any problems, please contact our Customer Care team at 

_[customercare@brownsfashion.com](mailto:customercare@brownsfashion.com)_

or call +44 (0) 203 750 1241 between 9:00am - 6:00pm GMT or +1 (404) 793 0378 between 9am - 6pm (PST) Monday to Friday.

##### Collect from our London Boutiques

We like to give you options – so if it suits you to pick up your order in one of our stores, instead of opting for delivery to your home… then you can! 

It’s pretty simple – once you’ve finished adding items to you Bag and you proceed to checkout simply select ‘Click from Boutique' as your delivery method, free of charge, and then your preferred Browns boutique. Easy, right?

Then it’s just business as usual, we will proceed with payment to complete the order and you can expect an email from us to confirm when the order is ready for pick up (usually 1-2 days). Finally, if you have ordered multiple items there’s a chance they might arrive at your chosen boutique at different times, but don’t worry – we will always keep you updated.

##### Order Verification

Orders may be subject to payment verification. For the protection of our customers, we want to ensure that every order we ship out is authorised by the cardholder. If your order is placed on hold, we will reach out to you immediately to ensure that any delays are minimal.  

##### Payment

We like to be accommodating, so we’re giving you lots of options to put your payment through*

  * Worldwide - Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Delta, Visa Electron, Diners Club International, JCB, PayPal, Union Pay
  * China, Taiwan, Hong Kong, Macau - All worldwide methods and Alipay
  * Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Belgium - All worldwide methods and Sofort
  * Netherlands - All worldwide methods and iDeal

*Some cards may require authorisation from the issuing bank.

##### Shipping

Browns offers worldwide shipping by partnering with premium carriers (so have your signature at the ready when the postman arrives!) Oh, and any first time orders must be shipped to the billing address of your credit card so that we can make sure there’s no funny business going on.

Side note: We do not ship on the weekend or bank holidays; therefore your order will be processed the next working day.

Please select your shipping destination from the list of countries below to display the available options and charges.

* * *

##### Delivery

**London Same Day Delivery**

When you just can’t wait to get your hands on some newness, Browns has you covered with same day delivery in specific areas of London, Monday to Saturday (excluding bank holidays, because even the postman needs a holiday too you know). Orders received and processed before 11am will arrive that very day to have you kitted out! And don’t worry, if you miss the 11am deadline we will swiftly deliver the following business day.

FYI: If you were trigger happy and purchased a few different items, you may encounter two deliveries as our items can come from two separate warehouses.

The delivery window for Same Day Delivery orders is usuallly between 4pm - 6pm. If you need to make changes to your shipping address or delivery time please _[click here](mailto:customercare@brownsfashion.com)_ ; likewise should the carrier be unable to deliver your order, the package will be returned to Browns and a refund will be issued. 

**Collect from our London Boutiques**

What’s better than the convenience of picking up your order in store at one of our _boutiques_? Well… it’s free! Now that’s always good news.

From the time when our team receive your order we anticipate it will usually take around 1-2 days for your order to be ready for pick up in the selected boutique – but we manage this by keeping you up to date via email, so keep an eye out!

Always bring along a photo ID and the confirmation email so we can be sure your order is going to the right person. If we don’t see you within 5 days, we’ll send you a little reminder to your inbox, and if we don’t see you in 7 days we will arrange a refund as unfortunately we can’t hold onto order for too long…

**UK Delivery**

Orders shipping to the United Kingdom will be coming to a postbox near you via DHL express post within 2-4 days.

Shipping times can vary, but we will always work hard to get your parcel to you ASAP. Deliveries will be made from Monday to Friday between 9:00am - 5:00pm.

**EU Delivery**

The Europeans love to stay ahead of the fashion game, so Browns will be pushing out those packages in 1-4 working days after your order has been processed. Deliveries will be made between Monday to Friday between 9:00am - 5:00pm, but just to let know you know - sometimes there are some delays due to customs clearance which Browns cannot be held accountable for, so please forgive us if you have to wait a few days longer.

**International (Non EU) Delivery**

The international deliveries have a little further to travel, so it’s only natural to expect a few extra days to receive your new things (usually delivering within 3-7 working days). Deliveries will be made between Monday to Friday between 9:00am - 5:00pm, but once again please be mindful of delays via customs clearance.

Please see delivery costs below. If you can't find your country, please contact  _customer care _for more information on delivery costs. 

##### Processing Time

We will always aim to dispatch your order within 48 hours pending product availability and credit verification, we make it our business to ensure a timely delivery of your order!

Please bear in mind that time frames are an estimation and can sometimes take a little longer during sale periods when we’re run off our favourite Louboutins!

##### Track My Order

We know there’s nothing worse than watching the clock waiting for your package to arrive, so Browns will always provide you with the necessary tracking information to watch your package like a hawk whether it’s travelling by land or sea (and of course we will always insure your package right up until arrival, naturally). Track your order;

  1. Log In to _'My Account'_
  2. Go to 'Order & Returns'
  3. Click on the 'View Order' of the purchase you would like to track
  4. Click on the tracking link that appears below each item

##### Shipping Restrictions

Due to international trading agreements, Browns must play by the rules and adhere to specific shipping agreements. If your package is delivering to Turkey, our Customer Care team will contact you directly prior to dispatch to obtain the required ID as per Turkish regulation. Furthermore, shipments to the Republic of Korea will be sent with a commercial invoice including relevant FTA declarations.

Please find all other restrictions listed below;

**United States**

US customers may be requested by US Customs to provide their IRS, EIN or SSN number before deliveries can be released to the given address. Customers will be given one week to provide this information. 

**Russia**

  * Delivery takes between 3-4 days.
  * Your order will not be taxed unless your monthly import allowance exceeds the €1000 price point and/or weight limit of 31kg.
  * If your order exceeds the above import allowance, tax to be paid is 30% of the exceeding amount.
  * For the registration and correct handling procedures, you will be required to submit a copy of your passport (and any other additional paperwork as per their request).

##### Duties & Taxes

When it comes to the cost of import duties on orders, we can’t cover everyone… almost, but not quite. For the below countries, the price you see is the price you pay. This includes your import duties.

  * Australia
  * Austria
  * Belgium
  * Bulgaria
  * Canada
  * China
  * Croatia
  * Cyprus
  * Czech Republic
  * Denmark
  * Estonia
  * Finland
  * France
  * Germany
  * Greece
  * Hungary
  * India
  * Ireland
  * Israel
  * Italy
  * Japan
  * Korea, Republic of
  * Kuwait
  * Latvia
  * Lithuania
  * Luxembourg
  * Malta
  * Mexico
  * Netherlands
  * Norway
  * New Zealand
  * Portugal
  * Puerto Rico
  * Qatar
  * Romania
  * Saudi Arabia
  * Singapore
  * Slovakia
  * Slovenia
  * Spain
  * Sweden
  * Switzerland
  * Taiwan (ROC)
  * Thailand
  * United Arab Emirates
  * United Kingdom
  * United States of America

For all other customers, the import duty is not included in the listed online price. As a customer you will be responsible for import duties/taxes incurred in the destination country.

There may be a chance that you will have to pay import duties when you come to pick up your order (or even at a later date, depending on the customs authority). Please note that we don't have visibilty of customs costs. 

We know this can be a tad confusing, so feel free to ask us any questions _here._

##### Same Day Delivery Locations

**London**

BR1, BR2, BR3, BR4, BR5, BR6, BR7, BR8, BR98, CR0, CR2, CR3, CR4, CR5, CR6, CR7, CR8, CR9, CR44, CR90, DA1, DA2, DA3, DA4, DA5, DA6, DA7, DA8, DA9, DA10, DA11, DA12, DA13, DA14, DA15, DA16, DA17, DA18, E1, E1W, E2, E3, E4, E5, E6, E7, E8, E9, E10, E11, E12, E13, E14, E15, E16, E17, E18, E20, E77, E98, EC1A, EC1M, EC1N, EC1P, EC1R, EC1V, EC1Y, EC2A, EC2M, EC2N, EC2P, EC2R, EC2V, EC2Y, EC3A, EC3B, EC3M, EC3N, EC3P, EC3R, EC3V, EC4A, EC4M, EC4N, EC4P, EC4R, EC4V, EC4Y, EC50, EC88, EN1, EN2, EN3, EN4, EN5, EN6, EN7, EN8, EN9, EN10, EN11, EN77, HA0, HA1, HA2, HA3, HA4, HA5, HA6, HA7, HA8, HA9, IG1, IG2, IG3, IG4, IG5, IG6, IG7, IG8, IG9, IG10, IG11, KT1, KT2, KT3, KT4, KT5, KT6, KT7, KT8, KT9, KT10, KT11, KT12, KT13, KT14, KT15, KT16, KT17, KT18, KT19, KT20, KT21, KT22, KT23, KT24, N1, N1C, N1P, N2, N3, N4, N5, N6, N7, N8, N9, N10, N11, N12, N13, N14, N15, N16, N17, N18, N19, N20, N21, N22, N81, NW1, NW1W, NW2, NW3, NW4, NW5, NW6, NW7, NW8, NW9, NW10, NW11, NW26, RM1, RM2, RM3, RM4, RM5, RM6, RM7, RM8, RM9, RM10, RM11, RM12, RM13, RM14, RM15, RM16, RM17, RM18, RM19, RM20, RM50, SE1, SE1P, SE2, SE3, SE4, SE5, SE6, SE7, SE8, SE9, SE10, SE11, SE12, SE13, SE14, SE15, SE16, SE17, SE18, SE19, SE20, SE21, SE22, SE23, SE24, SE25, SE26, SE27, SE28, SE99, SM1, SM2, SM3, SM4, SM5, SM6, SM7, SW1A, SW1E, SW1H, SW1P, SW1V, SW1W, SW1X, SW1Y, SW2, SW3, SW4, SW5, SW6, SW7, SW8, SW9, SW10, SW11, SW12, SW13, SW14, SW15, SW16, SW17, SW18, SW19, SW20, SW95, SW99, TW1, TW2, TW3, TW4, TW5, TW6, TW7, TW8, TW9, TW10, TW11, TW12, TW13, TW14, TW15, TW16, TW17, TW18, TW19, TW20, UB1, UB2, UB3, UB4, UB5, UB6, UB7, UB8, UB9, UB10, UB11, UB18, W1A, W1B, W1C, W1D, W1E, W1F, W1G, W1H, W1J, W1K, W1M, W1N, W1P, W1R, W1S, W1T, W1U, W1V, W1W, W1X, W1Y, W2, W3, W4, W5, W6, W7, W8, W9, W10, W11, W12, W13, W14, WC1A, WC1B, WC1E, WC1H, WC1N, WC1R, WC1V, WC1X, WC2A, WC2B, WC2E, WC2H, WC2N, WC2R, WC99, WD1, WD2, WD3, WD4, WD5, WD6, WD7, WD17, WD18, WD19, WD23, WD24, WD25, WD99

##### Returns

To make this process as quick and easy as possible, Browns offers customers a Free Returns Collection Service on all orders to take away the fuss. We recommend booking the service within 7 days of receiving your order to ensure it arrives safely back in our hands before the 14 day return window expires.

##### Free Returns Collection Service

To make this process as quick and easy as possible, Browns offers all customers a Free Returns Collection Service to take away the fuss. We recommend booking the service within 7 days of receiving your order to ensure it arrives safely back in our hands before the 14 day return window expires.

Oh, and please note that we can only collect your return from the same country to which we shipped your order to. Right, so how to book?

  1. Log in to _[‘My Account’](https://www.brownsfashion.com/uk/account/myaccount)_
  2. Go to _[‘Orders& Returns’](https://www.brownsfashion.com/uk/account/myaccount)_
  3. Click ‘Book A Return Collection’ next to the order you wish to return
  4. Select the item/s you would like to return and follow the steps to schedule a pick up time and address  

Keep an eagle eye on your inbox as we will be sending you;

  * Returns Merchandise Authorisation (RMA) Number

  * Confirmation of your collection time and address

  * Booking reference

  * Returns documents

Here are the non-negotiables (please make sure you follow these steps);

  1. Print out a copy of the Air Waybill (AWB) and attach the first page to the outside of your package, and hand the second page to your courier. We advise saving a copy for your records too as this is how you can track your shipment.

  2. If you have been provided with a Returns Invoice for Customs, please enclose one inside the package and attach a signed copy to the outside of the package with the AWB.

  3. DO NOT seal your package until the driver has checked the contents. But once you have the A-OK, seal away!

##### Conditions

Items must be returned unworn, unwashed, undamaged, unused and with all original tags attached to be in a returnable condition. We will not accept any items that are customised or personalised.

Where possible, any designer packaging such as authenticity cards, dust bags and leather tags must also be returned as they are considered part of the product.

If you receive an item which is damaged, please contact 

_Customer Care immediately._

**Footwear & Accessories:**  
Footwear and accessories must be returned unmarked and unscuffed in the original undamaged boxes provided and inside a protective shipping box.

**Swimwear:**  
For sanitary reasons please try on all swimwear over your own lingerie garments. Do not remove the protective slip.

Hosiery must be returned in its unopened package.

**Cosmetics:**  
All cosmetics must be returned unused, unopened with an unbroken seal and in its original packaging.

##### Refunds

Once your order has been received by our warehouse and complies with our 

_Returns Policy_

, a refund will be issued via the original payment method. Additionally, you will receive a refund confirmation email (just to make sure all our ducks are in a row).

FYI: Returned items will be refunded excluding the original cost of shipping and can take up to 14 working days to process. To read the returns policy in its entirety please 

_click here_.

##### How To Shop FAQs

**What payment methods do Browns accept?**

  * Worldwide - Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Delta, Visa Electron, Paypal (Paypal not accepted in Korea)
  * China, Taiwan, Hong Kong, Macau - All worldwide methods and Alipay
  * Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Belgium - All worldwide methods and Sofort
  * Netherlands - All worldwide methods and iDeal

**How will I know if you have received my order?**  
Once you’ve checked out with Browns (the order of course…) we will be swiftly sending an email your way to acknowledge we’ve received your order, yay! Note: this is only receipt of your order, not confirmation that your purchase has been made.

Now it’s all systems go… our amazing team will handpick your item/s while simultaneously verifying your payment and delivery details. If it all checks out, then it’s time to get that package outta here and on its way to you!

**What if an item is out of stock?**  
Browns is built on providing our customers with the most exclusive edit of luxury designers from all over the world. Due to the nature of our edit, quantities are limited and in some instances a one-off.

On the rare occasion an item is sold simultaneously to multiple customers online the stock information may become temporarily inaccurate. In this case, we will either cancel your order in full or just the items which are unavailable and proceed with the rest of the order.

**Do you offer same day delivery in London?**  
Keeping Londoners stylish every day we offer same day delivery in specific areas of London from Monday - Friday. To check out all the finer details click here.

**What happens if I notice that my personal details are incorrect after I have completed the ordered process?**  
Slippery fingers? It’s okay, we know it was a mistake. If you realise your personal details are incorrect, hop to it and send an [_email to our Customer Care team_](mailto:customercare@brownsfashion.com) \- and don’t forget to include your order number and we will do everything we can to rectify this mistake.

**Is it safe to use my credit card online at Browns?**  
We want to ensure you always have a safe and seamless experience online at Browns, therefore all orders are processed through a highly secure checkout system provided by Adyen.

To make things even easier - you can also store your credit card details in _[‘My Account’](https://www.brownsfashion.com/uk/account/myaccount)_ for future purchases. Consider this a circle of trust.

**How do I know if an item will fit me?**  
If you’re second guessing a purchase because you are unsure of the fit, please make sure you reference our comprehensive Fit Information and Size Guide that is listed on each product page. All products are sold by the international sizing schemes used by the designer (and we will always make sure we tell you if an item runs small or large to size). Take a gander over our product descriptions for all the details, not only are they entertaining but highly informative.

##### Shipping & Delivery FAQs

**Can I track my order online?**  
We know there’s nothing worse than watching the clock and waiting for your package to arrive, so Browns will not only provide you with regular email updates on the status of your order, but if you log in to [‘My Account’](https://www.brownsfashion.com/uk/account/myaccount) you can also find the tracking number to keep an eagle eye on the precious cargo.

**How much are the custom duties and taxes for my order?**  
When it comes to the cost of import duties on orders, we can’t cover everyone… almost, but not quite. For the below countries, the price you see is the price you pay.

  * Australia
  * Austria
  * Belgium
  * Bulgaria
  * Canada
  * China
  * Croatia
  * Cyprus
  * Czech Republic
  * Denmark
  * Estonia
  * Finland
  * France
  * Germany
  * Greece
  * Hungary
  * India
  * Ireland
  * Israel
  * Italy
  * Japan
  * Korea, Republic of
  * Kuwait
  * Latvia
  * Lithuania
  * Luxembourg
  * Malta
  * Mexico
  * Netherlands
  * Norway
  * New Zealand
  * Portugal
  * Puerto Rico
  * Qatar
  * Romania
  * Saudi Arabia
  * Singapore
  * Slovakia
  * Slovenia
  * Spain
  * Sweden
  * Switzerland
  * Taiwan (ROC)
  * Thailand
  * United Arab Emirates
  * United Kingdom
  * United States of America

For all other customers, the import duty is not included in the online listed price. As a customer you will be responsible for import duties/taxes incurred in the destination country, and there may be a chance this will occur when you come to pick up your order (or even at a later date, depending on the customs authority).

We know this can be a tad confusing, so feel free to ask us any questions _here_

##### My Account FAQs

**Do I need an account to place an order online?**  
We want to get to know you so that we can personalise your shopping experience. Therefore, upon placing an order you will be required to set up an account so that we can keep track all your details under one fashionable ‘cloud-like’ roof.

Think of your account like a secure little box which holds all the important things in one place like credit cards, shipping information, orders and of the course that dreamy wish list.

**How do I create an account on brownsfashion.com?**  
If you can find a way to drag yourself away from our new arrivals, go to '[My Account](https://www.brownsfashion.com/gb/account/login?returnUrl=%2fgb%2fcustomer-service)' in the top navigation and fill in your details.

**Is my personal information kept private?**  
We need you to know that any information you share with Browns is 100% private and confidential. At no point will we share, rent or sell your personal information, we want you all to ourselves! :)

##### Returns & Refunds FAQs

**Can I return my order?**  
We hope that our customers love each and every purchase. However, if it’s not feeling quite right then we want you to know you have options.

Perhaps you’ve changed your mind? The fit just doesn’t work, or the quality just wasn’t at the standard you expected. Your peace of mind is our priority, so let’s take it step by step.

**How do I return an item?**  
We have a few different ways to return items to Browns.

Browns offers a free collection service for returns - so why not use it! Our recommendation is that you book your collection within 7 days of receiving the order to ensure it arrives safely back in our hands before the 14 days are up.

  1. Log in to [‘My Account’](https://www.brownsfashion.com/uk/account/myaccount)
  2. Go to ['Orders & Returns'](https://www.brownsfashion.com/uk/account/myaccount)
  3. Click ‘Book A Return Collection’ next to the order you wish to return
  4. Select the item/s you would like to return and follow the steps to schedule a pick up time and address

Keep an eagle eye on your inbox as we will be sending you;

  * Returns Merchandise Authorisation (RMA) Number

  * Confirmation of your collection time and address

  * Booking reference

  * Returns documents

If you don’t want to use our free collection service please get in touch with our Customer Care team within 48 hours of receiving your order to request an RMA number. To finalise your return please address the package to;

Browns Returns  
Clippers Logistics  
43 Suez Road Brimsdown  
EN3 7SN United Kingdom

All returns via this method must include the RMA number clearly written on the original receipt and placed inside the returned package (any returns without these items will not be accepted).

We recommend items be returned via registered post or DHL as Browns will not be responsible for goods lost or damaged in transit.

Unfortunately at this time, beautiful items purchased online cannot be returned in store. So please adhere to one of the methods above!

**When will I receive my refund?**  
Once your return has been received by our warehouse and complies with our Returns Policy, you will be refunded via your original payment method. Please be aware that returned payments can take up to 14 working days to process depending on your bank or payment provider. Returned items will be refunded excluding the original cost of shipping.

**If my order has been cancelled, when will I receive my refund?**  
If you paid by debit card or PayPal, payment will usually be taken immediately. Therefore, once your has been cancelled you will be refunded accordingly.

If you paid by credit card, payment will usually be taken once your order is approved and ready for shipping. Please be aware that your bank or card issuer may reserve the money, meaning that you can't use it for a short period. If you cancel your order before it is processed, we will simply cancel the transaction and there will be no need to process a refund.

**Will customs duties, sales tax or VAT be refunded on a return?**  
If you are a customer in the European Union, USA, Canada, China, Australia, Puerto Rico, Switzerland, Singapore, Republic Of Korea, Kuwait, Qatar, India, Norway, Saudi Arabia, Taiwan, Thailand, U.A.E., Japan, you will be refunded the cost of your order including any sales tax and import duties that were applicable at the time of your purchase, excluding the original shipping cost.

All other customers will be refunded the cost of your order including any VAT or sales tax that were applicable at the time of your purchase, but excluding the original shipping cost and any import duties incurred to receive your order. You may be able to recover import duties for returned items by contacting your local customs bureau directly.

**Can I exchange my item?**  
If you would like to exchange an item, you will need to return the original item and then place a new order. You will receive a refund for the original item, excluding the original cost of shipping in accordance with our Returns Policy.

##### South Molton Street

23-27 South Molton Street  
London W1K 5RD

**Womenswear**

Phone: +44 (0) 20 7514 0016  
Email: _[womenswear@brownsfashion.com](mailto:womenswear@brownsfashion.com)_

**Menswear**

Phone: +44 (0) 20 7514 0038  
Email:  _[mens@brownsfashion.com](mailto:mens@brownsfashion.com)_  

**Opening Hours**

Monday: 10:00am - 7:00pm  
Tuesday: 10:00am - 7:00pm  
Wednesday: 10:00am - 7:00pm  
Thursday: 10:00am - 8:00pm  
Friday: 10:00am - 8:00pm  
Saturday: 10:00am - 7:00pm  
Sunday: 12:00pm - 6:00pm

##### Browns East

##### 21 Club Row  
London [E](https://www.google.co.uk/maps/place/Browns/@51.4941104,-0.1601695,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x4876053913741d05:0xd068ac7e1c23d62f!8m2!3d51.4941104!4d-0.1579808)[2 7EY](https://www.google.co.uk/maps/place/21+Club+Row,+London+E2+7EY/@51.5247484,-0.076734,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x48761cb768c63ae1:0xc956aefa85a84885!8m2!3d51.5247451!4d-0.0745453)

Phone: +44 (0) 207 729 2666  
Email:  _[brownseast@brownsfashion.com](mailto:brownseast@brownsfashion.com)_

**Opening Hours**

Monday: 11:00am - 6:30pm  
Tuesday: 11:00am - 6:30pm  
Wednesday: 11:00am - 6:300pm  
Thursday: 11:00am - 6:30pm  
Friday: 11:00am - 6:30pm  
Saturday: 10:00am - 6:30pm  
Sunday: 11:00am - 5:00pm  

##### Promotions & Competitions

**GENERAL**

  1. These terms and conditions (the ‘Standard Terms’), together with the terms and conditions that are specific to any Browns Competition (as defined below) (the individual 'Competition Terms'), are known as the 'Rules'. Capitalised words used in the Competition Terms shall have the same meaning as given to them in these Standard Terms. In the event of any conflict between the Competition Terms and these Standard Terms, the Competition Terms shall prevail.
  2. The Rules apply to any competition that is promoted on the Browns website (www.brownsfashion.com) or any Browns official social media page (@brownsfashion and @brownsmens) and is promoted by Browns (South Molton Street) Limited (‘Browns’), (a 'Competition').
  3. By entering a Competition, you agree to be bound by the Rules.
  4. Browns reserves the right to cancel or amend all or any part of a Competition and/or the Rules without notice for any event that is outside of Brown’s reasonable control. Any changes to the Rules, or cancellation of a Competition, will be posted on the Browns website (www.Browns.com). It is the responsibility of entrants to keep themselves informed of any changes to the Rules.
  5. In the event of any dispute regarding: (a) the Rules, (b) the conduct or results of the Competition, and/or (c) any other matter relating to a Competition (including the terms on which Browns and/or the judges award or have awarded a Prize), then the: (i) decision of Browns and/or the judges (as applicable) shall be final and unchallengeable, and (ii) no correspondence or discussion shall be entered into, comment issued, or reason given in respect of any decision made by Browns.

**COMPETITION ENTRANTS**

  6. By entering the Competition, you hereby warrant that all information and imagery submitted by you in your entry is yours, and is true, accurate and complete in every respect. Browns reserves the right to verify any information contained in your entry and/or your eligibility to enter the Competition.
  7. The Competition is only open to persons who are aged 18 or older on the date of launch of the Competition. 
  8. Entrants may be required to provide proof of identity and age.
  9. Where a Competition is open to persons who are residing outside of the United Kingdom, no person may enter the Competition if the Competition breaches any law or regulation of the jurisdiction in which they are resident.
  10. Browns reserves the right in its absolute discretion to disqualify any entrant if it has reasonable grounds to believe that an entrant has breached any of the Rules, any applicable law (including copyright law) or has otherwise infringed the intellectual property of any other person. Each entrant acknowledges and agrees that any failure to comply with the Rules could lead to Browns disqualifying that person, without Browns giving any reason for such disqualification or granting any opportunity for challenge.
  11. Any person that is: (a) an employee of any company involved in the Competition (including Browns); or (b) a family member of such employee, is not eligible to enter the Competition.  Browns reserves the right to disqualify any person that it knows is, or has reasonable grounds to believe is, ineligible for the Competition as a result of this Rule.
  12. In the event that a Prize-winner is disqualified from the Competition, Browns will, unless otherwise stated in the Competition Terms, select an alternative Prize-winner in the same manner as the original Prize-winner and such selection will be subject to the Rules.

**COMPETITION ENTRIES**

  13. Entries must be made by the closing date of a Competition and in the manner set out in the Competition Terms. Failure to do so will result in disqualification.
  14. There is no requirement to make any purchase in order to enter the Competition.
  15. Unless otherwise stated in the Competition Terms, only one entry per person is permitted. In the event that Browns discovers or has reasonable grounds to believe that the same person has made multiple Entries, such person and any Entries made by them shall be disqualified and, if such Entrant has already been selected as a Prize-winner, an alternative Prize-winner will be selected in accordance with Rule 10 above.
  16. Browns accepts no responsibility for the return of any entries.
  17. Browns will be able (in its sole discretion) to re-gram (on Instagram) or use on any of the Browns social media pages any Competition entries without notice, and you accept this use and that such use will be archived after the closing date of the Competition.  

**PRIZE-WINNERS**

  18. Prizes for winners (on the terms of these Standard Terms and Conditions) of a Competition will be set out in the Rules for each Competition (‘Prizes’). 
  19. Prize-winners will be selected and notified either in the manner set out in the Competition Terms, or through direct message on their Instagram or Twitter (or other social media used to enter the Competition) page. No prize will be awarded where any entrant has committed any form of misconduct (as determined by Browns in its sole discretion).
  20. Where entries are judged on artistic or other subjective criteria, Browns reserves the right to set and/or amend the criteria used to judge entries.
  21. Prizes are non-transferable and there is no cash alternative. In the event of a Prize being unavailable for any reason Browns reserves the right to substitute prizes of equal or greater value at any time.
  22. Prizes must be accepted by a Prize-winner. In the event that any Prize notification is returned as undeliverable or any Prize-winner fails to validly reply to a Prize notification within 14 days, Browns reserves the right to disqualify the Prize-winner and select an alternative Prize-winner in accordance with Rule 10 above.
  23. The value of a Prize may be taxable as income. The receipt by any winner of any of the Prize components of a Competition is conditioned upon compliance with any and all local, federal and state rules and regulations. The winner is solely responsible for all insurance and any and all applicable federal, state and local taxes that become due with respect to the prize.

**LIABILITY**

  24. Browns accepts no responsibility for any damage, loss, injury (other than our liability for personal injury or death as a result of our negligence) or disappointment of any kind suffered by any entrant in entering the Competition, including as a result of any entrant winning or not winning any prize.
  25. Browns accepts no responsibility for entries lost, damaged or delayed in the post, or due to computer error in transit. Entries made online using methods generated by a computer, script, macro or the use of automated devices to enter any Competition will be void.
  26. You are responsible for determining if entering into this Competition is lawful in your jurisdiction. To the extent that it is determined to be unlawful then Browns may void any such entry into the Competition and reserves the right to void any agreement which may be deemed to have been entered into between you and Browns by the action of law.

**INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS AND DATA PROTECTION**

  27. You agree that Browns (and any third party authorised by Browns) may use your entry (whether or not it wins the Competition) for any promotional purpose (for example, placing it on the Browns website or on any poster, leaflet or other advertising media). You confirm that your entry is original that you own and have the right to license to Browns the copyright and other intellectual property rights in the Entry for the purposes referred to in these Rules. You will retain ownership of copyright in your entry but you give Browns (and any third party authorised by Browns) your irrevocable permission to use, reproduce, publish, display, transmit, copy, amend, store, sell and sub-licence your entry worldwide for such promotional purposes and for the purposes of the Competition.
  28. Browns will use any personal information that you provide with your entry for the purposes of the Competition and, where you have given your consent, for marketing purposes. Any personal information relating to entrants will be used solely by us in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.
  29. All Prize-winners unconditionally agree (as a condition of accepting any prize) to: (a) the use of their name, one or more photographs of themselves and disclosure of their country of residence (if such Prize-winner is resident outside the UK); and (b) co-operate with or participate in any other reasonable post-Competition publicity.

**GOVERNING LAW AND JURISDICTION**

  30. The Rules and any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with them or their subject matter (including the Competition), existence, negotiation, validity, termination or enforceability (including non-contractual disputes or claims) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with English law.
  31. The Courts of England shall have exclusive jurisdiction in relation to any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with the Rules or their subject matter, existence, negotiation, validity, termination or enforceability (including non-contractual disputes or claims).

**COPIES OF THESE RULES**

  32. A copy of these Rules may be obtained by sending a stamped addressed envelope to: Legal Department, Browns UK Limited, Floor 4, The Bower, 211 Old Street, London EC1V 9NR, United Kingdom.

##### Terms & Conditions

**Introduction**

These Terms & Conditions (together with the information and policies contained in the "Customer Care" pages on the website and any other documents referred in these Terms & Conditions) ( **Terms & Conditions**) set out the legal terms that apply to your use of the website [http://www.brownsfashion.com](https://www.brownsfashion.com/uk/) ( **Website** or **Site** ), the purchase of your products from Browns (South Molton Street) Limited (company number 06887728) VAT number: GB 204 0769 35) whose registered office is at The Bower, 211 Old Street, London EC1V 9NR United Kingdom (“ **Browns Fashion** ”, **we** , **us** and **our** ) and the services ( **Services** ) that are provided by our parent company, Farfetch UK Limited and/or Farfetch.com US LLC depending on your location (Farfetch), under its trading division Black & White, as more particularly detailed below in the section headed Operation of Website and Services and Product.

You may not always be charged in the currency of your local area. To see all currencies you will be charged in please reference the location preferences page _here._ Your purchase of any of the products offered on the Site ( **Products** ) is subject to these Terms & Conditions and by placing an order for any Product you agree to be bound by them. You should print a copy of these Terms & Conditions for future reference. Use of your personal information submitted to or via the Site is governed by our [Privacy and Cookies Policy.](https://www.brownsfashion.com/uk/customer-service#cs-csmenu-7)

We reserve the right to change these Terms & Conditions from time to time by changing them on the Site, although no such change will affect any order you have already placed with us.

**Access to the Site**

It is your responsibility to ensure your equipment (computer, laptop, netbook, tablet or other mobile device) meets all the necessary technical specifications to enable you to access and use the Site and is compatible with the Site.

We may, from time to time, restrict access to certain features, parts or content of the Site, or the entire Site, to users who have registered with us. You must ensure that any registration details you provide are accurate. If you choose, or you are provided with, a log-on ID (such as a username and password or other identifier) as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential and must not reveal it to anyone else. You are responsible for all activities that occur under your log-on ID and must notify us immediately of any unauthorised use or other security breach of which you become aware. We reserve the right to disable any log-on ID, at any time, if in our opinion you have failed to comply with any of the provisions of these Terms & Conditions or if any details you provide for the purposes of registering as a user prove to be false.

**Operation of Website and Services and Product**  

_Operation of Website and delivery of Services_

The Website is owned by Browns Fashion. Browns Fashion has subcontracted the operation of certain aspects of the Website to Black & White, a trading division of Farfetch. As such, Farfetch provides and/or procures certain services on behalf of Browns Fashion to enable the operation of the Website and for you to search through the Website and purchase products from Browns Fashion. Such Services include, but are not limited to, payment processing, customer service  and hosting. Farfetch UK Limited is a company registered in England and Wales and its registered office is at The Bower, 211 Old Street, London EC1V 9NR, United Kingdom. Its registered company number is 06400760 and its VAT number is GB 204 0769 35. Farfetch.com US LLC is a company registered in the USA and its registered office is at 2301, East 7th Street, Suite A-250 Los Angeles, California, 90023.

_Products_

The Products are owned and sold on the Website by Browns Fashion.  Browns Fashion attempts to be as accurate as possible in the description of the Products. However, we cannot guarantee that any descriptions are totally accurate, complete, reliable or error-free. The images of the Products on the Website are for illustrative purposes only. Although we attempt to display the colours accurately, we cannot guarantee that your computer's display of the colours accurately reflects the colour of the Products.

As a consumer, you have legal rights in relation to products that are faulty or not as described. Advice about your legal rights is available from your local Citizens' Advice Bureau or Trading Standards office. Nothing in these Terms & Conditions will affect these legal rights.

The Products sold are supplied for your domestic and private use only. You agree that you will not use the Products for any commercial, business or re-sale purposes. Neither Browns Fashion nor Farfetch has any liability to you for any loss of profit, loss of business, business interruption, or loss of business opportunity.

**Ordering & Availability**

Products may be ordered by clicking on the items you wish to purchase and then following the prompts that will appear on-screen. You may check and correct any input errors in your order up until the point at which you submit your order to us by clicking the "Pay Now" button on the checkout page.

After placing an order, you will receive an email from us acknowledging that we have received your order and giving you an order reference number. Please note that this does not mean that your order has been accepted. Your order constitutes an offer to us to buy a Product. All orders are subject to acceptance by us. We are not obliged to accept your order and may, at our discretion, decline to accept any order. You do, however, acknowledge that by clicking on the "Pay Now" button, you enter into an obligation to pay for the Product(s). Where we accept your order, we will confirm such acceptance to you by sending you an email that confirms that the Product has been despatched ( **Despatch Confirmation** ). The contract between you and us in relation to the Product(s) ordered ( **Contract** ) will only be formed when we send you the Despatch Confirmation. After entering into the Contract, we will be under a legal duty to supply you with goods that are in conformity with the Contract.

The Contract will relate only to the Product(s) whose despatch we have confirmed in the Despatch Confirmation. We will not be obliged to supply any other Product(s) which may have been part of your order until the despatch of such Product(s) has been confirmed in a separate Despatch Confirmation.

**Delivery**

Your order will be fulfilled by the delivery date set out in the Despatch Confirmation or, if no delivery date is specified, then within 30 days after the date of the Despatch Confirmation, unless there are exceptional circumstances.

Your order will be delivered to the delivery address you specify when placing your order.

If your delivery address is geographically remote, for example certain outlying islands or other isolated locations, it is possible that we may not be able to deliver there. If that is the case, we will notify you before we accept your order. We reserve the right not to deliver to any country that is prohibited by applicable export laws. Orders cannot be delivered to PO Box or similar addresses.

Products comprised within the same order cannot be delivered to different addresses.

Deliveries are made by our trusted courier and take place on Monday to Saturday (or other normal working week days in countries that do not follow a Western pattern of working week), excluding bank and public holidays, usually within the hours of 8am and 5pm. It is not possible to specify a precise time at which a delivery will take place. Please note that the courier may require deliveries to be signed for.

If you order Product(s) for international delivery, they may be opened and inspected by customs authorities and may be subject to import duties and taxes which are levied when the delivery reaches the specified destination. You will be responsible for payment of any such import duties and taxes. Please note that we have no control over these charges and cannot predict their amount. Please contact your local customs office for further information before placing your order. In the event that you return an item, the import duties will be refunded if they were originally included in the purchase price. If they were not included then you will responsible for reclaiming duty directly from your local customs office.

Please also note that you must comply with all applicable laws and regulations of the country for which the Product(s) are destined. We will not be liable for any breach by you of any such laws.

**Risk & Ownership**

The Product(s) ordered will be at your risk from the time of delivery or collection (as the case may be). Ownership of the Product(s) ordered will also pass to you on delivery or collection (as the case may be), provided full payment of all sums due in respect of the Product(s), including any delivery charges, has been received.

**Price & Payment**

The price of Products is as quoted on the Site from time to time.

Prices include VAT but exclude delivery costs, which will be automatically added (at the cost shown) to the total amount due when you view the items in your shopping basket, and have selected your chosen different delivery method.

Prices and delivery costs are liable to change at any time, but changes will not affect orders in respect of which we have already sent you a Despatch Confirmation.

The Site contains a large number of Products and it is always possible that, despite our best efforts, some of the Products listed on the Site may be incorrectly priced. We will normally verify prices as part of our despatch procedures so that, where a Product's correct price is less than our stated price, we will charge you the lower amount. If a Product’s correct price is higher than the price stated on the Site, we will normally, at our discretion, either contact you for instructions before despatching the Product, or reject your order and notify you of such rejection.

Payment for all orders must be made by credit or debit card on the checkout page. We accept payment by most major credit and debit cards.

You should be aware that online payment transactions are subject to validation checks by your card issuer and we are not responsible if your card issuer declines to authorise payment for any reason. We also carry out a standard pre-authorisation check on your payment card, and Products will not be despatched until this pre-authorisation check has been completed. Please note, it is possible that your card issuer may charge you an online handling fee or processing fee. We are not responsible for this.

From time to time we may run promotions where we issue discount codes. These can be used in part-payment of the price of Product(s) ordered online, subject to the Terms & Conditions under which they were issued (as indicated in our relevant promotion from which you got the code). Discount codes can only be used once, and only during the period of validity stated and only in respect of the relevant Product(s) stated. Discount codes cannot be redeemed for cash.

**Returns Policy**

Returned Products must conform to our returns policy below.

You have a legal obligation to take reasonable care of the products while they are in your possession, and you must return them in the same condition in which you receive them (except to the extent reasonably necessary to examine them). This includes the following guidelines:

  * Products should be returned unworn (other than to try them on), unwashed, undamaged and unused with their original tags;
  * footwear and accessories should be returned in the original boxes provided and inside a protective shipping box;
  * if the Product comes with a security tag this should be left on;
  * hosiery should only be returned if it is unopened and is in its original package; and
  * lingerie and swimwear must only be tried on over your own lingerie garments.

If you fail to comply with the above obligations (including the conditions of return), we may deduct from the refund an amount to reflect the diminished value of the Product(s) up to the full price of the Product(s).

You cannot cancel a contract for the supply of any of the following Products:

  * any Products that have been personalised or made to your own bespoke specifications unless such Products were damaged or faulty when delivered to you or have been incorrectly delivered (see _Returns and refunds for customised Products below for more information_ ); and
  * any garments or cosmetics Products that have had a hygiene label or seal removed or broken.

_Returns and refunds for customised products_

Due to the nature of personalised and monogrammed Products, returns, changes or cancellations are at our discretion. In exercising this discretion, we will have regard to the level of customisation and personalisation and also reserve the right to offer a store credit rather than a monetary refund. Store credit is valid for 6 months from the date of issue. This does not affect your statutory rights. Please note, that personalised and/or customised Products may have a long lead in time before shipping, but payment will be taken at the time of or shortly after you submit your order and in advance of shipping.

_Returns Process_

We recommend that you return Products in their original packaging to ensure the necessary protection when in transit. Instructions for the return of the Product(s) will be included with the delivery package. When cancelling a purchase and returning Products to us you have two options available to you:

  1. Depending on where you live, exercise your right to cancel under the _Consumer Contracts (Information, Cancellation and Additional Charges) Regulations 2013 ( **CCRs** )_. If you choose this option you will be refunded the full price for the Product(s) (subject to our Returns Policy) and the cost of standard delivery but will be liable for the organisation and cost of returning the Product(s) to us.
  2. Use our Free Returns service. If you choose this option you can return the Products(s) for free and will be refunded the full price for the Product(s) (subject to our Returns Policy) but not the delivery charges.

We describe these two options in more detail below.

_(i) Your cancellation right under the Consumer Contracts (Information, Cancellation and Additional Charges) Regulations 2013 ( **CCRs** )_

Except in relation to certain types of Products (as set out _above_ ), you may cancel a contract at any time before your order is delivered and up to 14 days afterwards, beginning on the day after you received the Products ("cooling-off period").

To cancel a Contract, you must clearly inform us, preferably:

  * by email at customercare@brownsfashion.com or by telephone on **+44 (0)203 962 1241** giving us your name, address and order reference; or
  * by completing and returning the cancellation form [insert link] and sending it to the address set out in the form.

If you cancel an order (or part of an order) during the cooling off period, you must return the Product(s) within 14 days after the day on which you notify us of the cancellation and comply with the Returns Policy.

If you cancel a Contract between us within the 14 day cooling-off period (see above), we will process the refund due to you as soon as possible and, in any case within 14 days after the day on which we receive the Product(s) back or (ii) if earlier, the day on which we receive evidence that you have returned the Product(s) to our returns address.

We will refund the price of the Product(s) in full (subject to any deduction we are entitled to make due to your use of or damage to the Product(s)), including the cost of standard delivery. However, we will not refund your cost of returning the Product(s) to us, and you are responsible for those costs. We will refund any money received from you using the same method originally used by you to pay for your purchase, unless agreed otherwise.

_(ii) Free Returns Pick Up_

We offer a free collection service to all customers for Product(s) you wish to return except in relation to certain types of Products as set out in the Returns Policy. You have 14 days from receiving your order to return the Product to us. We strongly recommend that you book your free returns pick-up within 7 days of receiving your order to ensure that it arrives back in time. Please note that we can only collect returns from the same country to which your order was delivered.

To book a free returns pick-up:

  1. Log in to  _[‘My Account’](https://www.brownsfashion.com/uk/account/myaccount)_
  2. Go to  _[‘Orders& Returns’](https://www.brownsfashion.com/uk/account/myaccount)_
  3. Click ‘Book A Return Collection’ next to the order you wish to return
  4. Select the item/s you would like to return and follow the steps to schedule a pick up time and address

We will email you with your Returns Merchandise Authorisation (RMA) number, confirmation of your collection time and address, a booking reference number and returns documents.

_What Happens Next?_

Print out the Air Waybill (AWB) and attach it to the outside of the parcel. There will also be a copy to give to the courier. Please save a copy of the AWB for your records. You can use this to track your return shipment.

If you have been provided with a returns invoice for customs, please enclose one inside the package and attach a signed copy on the outside with the AWB.

Do not seal your package until the driver has checked the contents.

Please note that you have 30 days to contact us upon the pickup of your return to ensure that we have acknowledged it and received the Product. If you contact us after this 30 days period, we cannot guarantee a refund.

**Faulty Products**

If any Product you order is damaged or faulty when delivered to you or has developed a fault, you may have one or more legal remedies available to you, depending on when you make us aware of the problem, in accordance with your legal rights. If you believe a Product was delivered damaged or faulty or has developed a fault, you should inform us as soon as possible, preferably in writing, giving your name, address and order reference. Nothing in this section affects your legal rights.

**Product Information**

Whilst we have taken reasonable steps to depict Products as accurately as possible through the photographs and other images featured on the Site, the detailing (such as colour, pattern and texture, etc.) you see on-screen will depend on your monitor and, as such, may not exactly reflect the actual detailing of a Product when you receive it.

Any information on the Site regarding sizing of Products is included as a guide only. If you are in any doubt as to the size of any Product you require, we recommend that you contact us prior to placing an order (see _Contacting us_ ).

**What You Are Allowed To Do**

You may only use the Site for non-commercial use and only in accordance with these Terms & Conditions. You may retrieve and display content from the Site on a computer screen, print and copy individual pages and, subject to the next section, store such pages in electronic form. Additional terms may also apply to certain features, parts or content of the Site and, where they apply, will be displayed on-screen or accessible via a link.

**What You Are Not  Allowed To Do**

Except to the extent expressly set out in these Terms & Conditions, you are not allowed to:

  * 'scrape' content or store content of the Site on a server or other storage device connected to a network or create an electronic database by systematically downloading and storing all of the content of the Site;
  * remove or change any content of the Site or attempt to circumvent security or interfere with the proper working of the Site or the servers on which it is hosted; or 
  * create links to the Site from any other website, without our prior written consent, although you may link from a website that is operated by you provided the link is not misleading or deceptive and fairly indicates its destination, you do not imply that we endorse you, your website, or any products or services you offer, you link to (and do not frame or replicate) the home page of the Site, and the linked website does not contain any content that is unlawful, threatening, abusive, defamatory, pornographic, obscene, vulgar, indecent, offensive or which infringes on the intellectual property rights or other rights of any third party.

You must only use the Site and anything available from the Site for lawful purposes (complying with all applicable laws and regulations), in a responsible manner, and not in a way that might damage our name or reputation or that of any of our affiliates.

All rights granted to you under these Terms & Conditions will terminate immediately in the event that you are in breach of any of them.

**Intellectual Property Rights**

All intellectual property rights in any content of the Site (including text, graphics, software, photographs and other images, videos, sound, trade marks and logos) are owned by Farfetch, Browns Fashion or our licensors. Except as expressly set out here, nothing in these Terms & Conditions gives you any rights in respect of any intellectual property owned by us or our licensors and you acknowledge that you do not acquire any ownership rights by downloading content from the Site. In the event you print off, copy or store pages from the Site (only as permitted by these Terms & Conditions), you must ensure that any copyright, trade mark or other intellectual property right notices contained in the original content are reproduced.

**Content**

We may change the format and content of the Site from time to time. You agree that your use of the Site is on an 'as is' and 'as available' basis and at your sole risk.

Whilst we try to make sure that all information contained on the Site (other than any user-generated content) is correct, it is not intended to amount to authority or advice on which reliance should be placed. You should check with us or the relevant information source before acting on any such information.

We make or give no representation or warranty as to the accuracy, completeness, currency, correctness, reliability, integrity, quality, fitness for purpose or originality of any content of the Site and, to the fullest extent permitted by law, all implied warranties, conditions or other terms of any kind are hereby excluded and we accept no liability for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of you or anyone else using the Site or relying on any of its content.

We cannot and do not guarantee that any content of the Site will be free from viruses and/or other code that may have contaminating or destructive elements. It is your responsibility to implement appropriate IT security safeguards (including anti-virus and other security checks) to satisfy your particular requirements as to the safety and reliability of content.

**External Links**

The Site may, from time to time, include links to external sites, which may include links to third party offers and promotions. We include these to provide you with access to information, products or services that you may find useful or interesting. We are not responsible for the content of these sites or for anything provided by them and do not guarantee that they will be continuously available. The fact that we include links to such external sites does not imply any endorsement of or association with their operators or promoters.

**Our Liability**

Nothing in these Terms & Conditions shall limit or exclude our liability to you:

  * for death or personal injury caused by our negligence;
  * for fraudulent misrepresentation;
  * for breach of any term implied by the Consumer Rights Act 2015 and which, by law, may not be limited or excluded
  * under Part I of the Consumer Protection Act 1987; or
  * for any other liability that, by law, may not be limited or excluded.

Subject to this, in no event shall we be liable to you for any business losses and any liability we do have for losses you suffer arising from any Contract shall not exceed the purchase price of the relevant Product(s) and is strictly limited to losses that were reasonably foreseeable. Losses are foreseeable where they could be contemplated by you and us at the time your order is accepted by us.

We will not be liable or responsible for any failure to perform, or delay in performance of, any of our obligations under any Contract that is caused by events outside our reasonable control.

**General**

You may not transfer or assign any or all of your rights or obligations under any Contract.

All notices given by you to us must be given in writing to the address set out at the end of these Terms & Conditions. We may give notice to you at either the email or postal address you provide to us when placing an order.

If we fail to enforce any of our rights, that does not result in a waiver of that right.

If any provision of these Terms & Conditions is found to be unenforceable, all other provisions shall remain unaffected.

These Terms & Conditions may not be varied except with our express written consent.

These Terms & Conditions and any document expressly referred to in them represent the entire agreement between you and us in relation to the subject matter of any Contract. We are required by law to advise you that Contracts may be concluded in the English language only and that no public filing requirements apply.

These Terms & Conditions shall be governed by English law, and you agree that any dispute between you and us regarding them or any Contract will only be dealt with by the English courts, provided that, if you live in a part of the United Kingdom other than England, the applicable law of that part of the United Kingdom will govern and any dispute will only be dealt with by the courts there.

**Contact Us**

Please submit any questions you have about these Terms & Conditions or an order you have placed or ordering in general by:

**United Kingdom**  
Phone: +44 (0) 203 962 1241  
Monday - Sunday 9am - 6pm (GMT)  
English only

**United States**  
Phone: +1 (347) 983 6574  
Monday - Friday 9am - 6pm (PST)  
English only

**Email**  
Monday - Friday 9am - 2am (GMT)  
Saturday - Sunday 9am - 6pm (GMT)

Or please write to us at: Browns Fashion (Web Operations), 23-27 South Molton Street, London, W1K 5RD, United Kingdom

##### Privacy & Cookies Policy

**BROWNS PRIVACY POLICY (“PRIVACY POLICY”)**

Last updated: 25th May 2018

  1. **ABOUT BROWNS AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We are Browns (South Molton Street) Limited (“Browns”, “we”, “us”, “our”), and we are committed to protecting your privacy.

Browns (South Molton Street) Limited is the controller for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”), a company registered in England and Wales (Company Number 06887728), with its registered office located at The Bower, 4th Floor 211 Old street, London EC1V 9NR, United Kingdom. Browns is part of the Farfetch Group (www.farfetch.com).

This Privacy Policy provides information on how we collect and use personal data. Browns operates www.brownsfashion.com, various international websites (collectively, the "Website").

This Privacy Policy sets out the information that we collect, the reasons for which we collect that information, and how we can use and share that information.

The Website and the services provided by Browns are not intended to be used by children. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, you can contact our Data Protection Officer at [privacy@brownsfashion.com](mailto:privacy@brownsfashion.com).

  2. **THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

Our Website can contain links to and from the websites of our partner boutiques, advertisers, and affiliates, amongst others. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites. We are not responsible or liable for the privacy policies or practices of those websites, so please check their policies before you submit any personal data to those websites.

  3. **WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT, AND HOW?**

When you interact with us, whether by using our Website or communicating with us, we may collect the following information about you:

    * **information you give us:** you may give us information about yourself if you sign up for an account on our Website, place an order for products, complete any online forms (such as registration forms, competitions, and surveys), opt in to receive our newsletters and special offers, enter a competition or promotion, participate in social media functions with our Website, or correspond with us (by email, telephone, instant chat, social media or otherwise).

Depending on what you provide, this information can include your name, address or location, phone number and email address, date of birth, gender, purchase information, shopping preferences, images and financial information (including your credit or debit card details, although we do not hold them, our payment processors do).

If you register an account on the Website, then you may choose to give us your photograph and nickname. From your account, you can also invite your friends to shop at our Website (including by email, Facebook, or Twitter). Although we will let them know that we received their details from you, please ensure that you have the permission of your friends before sharing their contact details with us and only forward emails to people you know would be happy to receive them.

    * **information we receive from other accounts or sources:** we can receive information about you from other sources, such as from your other accounts or other websites, including data brokers, our partner boutiques, social media providers like Facebook and Twitter, advertising networks and analytics partners, and payment and delivery service providers.

By logging in to our mobile applications via Facebook or Twitter, or linking your account on our Website to your Facebook or Twitter accounts, you are giving us permission to obtain certain information and content from these accounts. The specific types of information that we may obtain depends on your settings for that account or website, and will be subject to their privacy policies.

We supplement the data you provide to us with data from data append services such as public or social graph data in order to better serve you with content or promotions. We will append this data to our existing customer account information to better understand customers’ interests and to provide more relevant product recommendations and advertising, to increase our customer’s security when using our Website and to comply with our legal obligations, such as sanctions laws. This information may include household size, household income, or profession. This information can be associated with your personal information such as name, email, address, physical address or phone number.

You can see more details about the third parties we use in Section 5 below.

    * **information our IT systems collect about you:** each time you visit the Website, certain information will be created and automatically recorded by our IT systems. That information includes:

      * cookies: you can see more details about cookies in Section 7 below, but these small text files can help improve your experience with the Website and make it easier to interact with us. This may include storing your location or language preferences to save you having to re-enter information when returning to, or ensuring that items you wish to order don’t disappear as you navigate between pages on, our Website. We also use cookies to provide you with tailored advertising;

      * device information: the information provided by your device will differ depending on which type of device you are using (whether it’s a PC, Mac, iPhone, Android, or otherwise) and the settings on that device, but includes the type of device you have (such as an iPhone 6S or Samsung Galaxy S7), the device’s IP address, the browser you are using, your mobile network provider (for mobile devices), the pages you have visited, your time zone and country location, and crash or download error reports.

    * **information we collect in store:** When you visit Browns East shop, you may have the opportunity to use pioneering technology to enhance your in-store experience. You may also give us information about yourself in-store if you make a purchase using a credit or debit card, complete a survey or questionnaire, enter a competition or promotion, provide us with feedback or otherwise interact or correspond with us in-store. Where you use a WiFi-enabled device in-store, certain information may be provided by your device, which will differ depending on your device and settings. The information that may be provided is the type of device you have, the device identifier/media access control (MAC) address, the proximity of the device from the access point, location of the device, and where relevant, when and for how long the device is connected to the Wi-Fi network. You can prevent information being provided by turning off the Wi-Fi feature on your device

  4. **WHAT DO YOU USE MY INFORMATION FOR?**

To provide you services and the Website, including to allow you to order and receive products using our Website, administer your account and to optimise your experience we need to use the information that we collect in a number of different ways.

We also use the information for marketing and advertising purposes. Where you have told us you would like to receive marketing communications or when you have made a purchase using our services, we and our partner boutiques will use your personal information (including your name, email address and address) to occasionally send you updates, news, and offers via email, post, or other forms of media. We may use your information (including supplemental information received from partners that we append to our existing customer information as described below), to tailor these messages to you. You may unsubscribe from email marketing communications by modifying your preferences in your account’s profile management section, or by following the opt out instructions in the promotional emails we send you.

We use third-party service providers to serve advertisements most relevant to you across your different devices and on our own and others’ websites and mobile applications. In addition to the information about your visits to our website or usage of our mobile application, our service providers may also use the information about your interactions with other websites or applications to target advertisements for products available from Browns. For information about opting out of targeted advertising and controlling the use of cookies, please see the cookies section of this Privacy Policy.

We also carry out research, analysis, and surveys on your use of our Website, and views. We keep tracking of your spend on our Website to see if you can benefit from our exclusive loyalty programs as the VIC customer program and Access. Finally we use your information to confirm your identity and perform credit checks or anti-fraud checks, in order to ensure your, and our, financial security.

Please note that we do not sell your information without your consent (whether your name, address, emails address, financial information, or otherwise) to any third party.

Please scroll down to find out the detailed purposes for which we collect your information, what specific information is collected and the legal basis for which we purpose that data.

Processing Purpose | Types of Data | Legal Basis  
---|---|---  
To register and manage your account in our Website | Name, email, password and other additional details you may wish to add in your account, like phone number addresses and gender. | Performance of a Contract with you  
To fulfil the orders you make through our website | Name, addresses, phone number, Order details, like the products you are buying, the size and price. | Performance of a Contract with you  
To collect payment from you | Payment information, which comprises the credit/debit card’s number, holder’s name and CCV – we do not store them and only transfer them to our authorized payment providers. | Performance of a Contract with you  
To provide you with our customer services (including helping you to solve any issue you have with our services, updating you about any change to our terms of service, or contacting you to know how was your experience with us) | Name, email, password and addresses and your contact history with us (including phone records of our conversations) | Contract and legitimate interests in retaining you as a customer  
To monitor the quality of our customer services | Name, email, password and addresses and your contact history with us | Legitimate interests in running our business  
To administer, maintain and optimise our Website and our services | Device information (such as your device IP address and device type), Cookie identifiers and browsing information | Legitimate interests in running our business  
To perform fraud and credit checks and if we can do business with you | Name; email; addresses; credit/debit card details; browsing history; purchase history; date of birth; gender; device information (such as IP address and device type), any national identifiers (like driver’s license or ID cards) and any publicly available information (like social media profiles or news) | Legitimate interests to protect Browns and its customers from fraudulent activities and compliance with a legal obligation  
To send you marketing communications and personalised offers | Name; Email; Phone Number; Addresses; Date of Birth;  
Purchase history; Browsing history and behaviour; Device information;  
Shopping preferences; Cookie identifiers; Internal identifiers; Country | Legitimate interests to electronic direct marketing of similar products and services to that which you have acquired using our Website or, when such is not applicable, your Consent.  
Analysis of your behaviour and purchases in our Website | Name; Email; Phone Number; Addresses; Date of Birth; Purchase history; Browsing history and behaviour; Device Information;  
Shopping preferences; Nickname; Cookie identifiers; Internal identifiers; Country; Spent tier level and Wealth. | Legitimate interests in running our business and improve our Website and your experience  
Carry on enquiries and surveys on your use of our website and views | Email; Device information, demographic information (including gender, country of residence and household income) and content of survey responses | Legitimate interests in running our business and improve our Website and your experience.  
Advertising and retarget advertising | Email; Cookie Identifiers; Device Information; | Legitimate Interests in running our business  
  5. **WHO DO YOU SHARE MY INFORMATION WITH?**

To provide the Website and our services, we work with a number of carefully selected third parties. To do this, we may share your information with these third parties in the following limited circumstances:

    * **Group companies for business purposes:** Browns (South Molton Street) Limited is part of a larger family of companies in different parts of the world. Our group of companies, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company, and that company’s subsidiaries as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006, includes Farfetch UK Limited, Fashion Concierge UK Limited, Farfetch Portugal – Unipessoal, Lda., Farfetch.com Limited, Farfetch.com US LLC., Farfetch.com Brasil Servicos LTDA, Farfetch Japan Co Ltd and Farfetch (Shanghai) E-Commerce Co. Ltd (the “Farfetch Group”). We may share your personal information in order to operate our business and provide the Website and services. Rest assured, their use of information is consistent with this Privacy Policy;

    * **Third party service providers for business purposes:** We have subcontracted the operation of certain aspects of the Site to Black & White, a trading division of Farfetch UK Limited (company number 06400760, VAT number GB 204 0769 35). Services provided or procured by Farfetch include, but are not limited to, payment processing, customer service, hosting and delivery logistics

    * **advertisers for marketing purposes:** we can provide your information to our advertising and social media partners (including Facebook and Twitter, where you choose) where they require the data to select and serve relevant adverts about our products and services to you and others;

    * **third parties where we are considering a corporate transaction:** the Farfetch Group is always looking for new opportunities and directions in which to grow, and that may take into account Browns. This means sometimes we may consider corporate transactions such as merger, acquisitions, reorganisations, asset sale, or similar. In these instances, we may transfer your information to enable the assessment and undertaking of that transaction. If we buy or sell any business or assets, your personal information may be one of the assets that are transferred;

    * **to comply with legal requests:** on occasion we may be required to liaise with various regulators and law enforcement agencies in a number of different countries, whether as a result of law, a court order, or another legal process. Although we dispute requests wherever suitable, in some cases we may have to share your information with the regulators or law enforcement agencies. Where we consider it appropriate, and provided we are not prohibited from doing so by law or court order, we will attempt to notify you of these legal demands; and

    * **aggregated information with third parties:** we may aggregate your information with the information of other customers, creating a dataset of information about the usage of our Website, purchase of products, and other general, grouped information about our customers on the basis of our legitimate interest to understand the usage of our service and demand for our product. Although this dataset is aggregated and anonymised, meaning it cannot identify you as an individual, it provides a valuable insight into the use of our Website and we may therefore share it with select third parties. These parties may include providers of plugins or similar technologies to help measure traffic, our partner boutiques and other providers to allow them to better stock products, and our investors. Please note that we do not share your information with any third party advertisers or networks for the provision of third party advertising on our Website.

  6. **TRANSFERS OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

To provide our Website and our services, in accordance with the purposes set out above, we or Farfetch UK Limited may transfer and store the personal information that we collect from you to a destination outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), mostly to the United States. When doing so, we rely on different adequacy measures, as stated below:

    * **Adequacy Decision:** We transfer the personal data that we collect from you to conduct fraud checks to Israel, which was found to have an adequate level of protection for personal data under Commission Decision 2011/61/EU of 31 January 2011.

    * **Privacy Shield:** Some third party providers based in the US, where we transfer your information to, comply with the US Department of Commerce's EU-US Privacy Shield and have certified that adhere to the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. For more information about the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Privacy Shield website.

    * **Model Clauses:** We rely in the Commission’s model contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries (i.e. the standard contractual clauses) pursuant to Decision 2010/87/EU when transferring your information to US service providers who do not adhere to the US Department of Commerce's EU-US Privacy Shield.

  7. **COOKIES**

We use technology such as "cookies" to collect information and store your online preferences. Cookies are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which allows the server to uniquely identify the browser on each page.

We use the following categories of cookies on our Website

    * CATEGORY 1: STRICTLY NECESSARY COOKIES These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you have asked for such as remembering your login details or shopping basket items cannot be provided.

    * CATEGORY 2: PERFORMANCE COOKIES These cookies collect anonymous information on how you use our Website. For example, we use Google Analytics cookies to help us understand how customers arrive at our site, browse or use our site and highlight areas where we can improve areas such as navigation, shopping experience and marketing campaigns. The data stored by these cookies does not show personal details from which your individual identity can be established. You may opt in to these cookies using your browser settings but it may affect the performance of our Website.

    * CATEGORY 3: FUNCTIONALITY COOKIES These cookies remember choices you make such as the country you visit our website from, language and search parameters such as size, colour or product line. These can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate to your selections and to make the visits more tailored and pleasant. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. You may opt in to these cookies using your browser settings but it may affect the functionality of our Website.

    * CATEGORY 4: TARGETING COOKIES OR ADVERTISING COOKIES These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advert as well as help measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. The cookies are usually placed by third party advertising networks. They remember the websites you visit and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers. For example, we use third party companies to provide you with more personalised adverts when visiting other websites. You may opt-in to these cookies using your browser settings.

    * CATEGORY 5: SOCIAL MEDIA COOKIES These cookies allow you to share what you’ve been doing on the website on social media such as Facebook and Twitter. Please refer to the respective privacy policies for how their cookies work.

If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the help and support area on your Internet browser for instructions on how to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at www.AboutCookies.org. Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our Website.

You can withdraw your consent to these cookies at any time through the following options:

    * Google Analytics cookies across all websites, please visit Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on;

    * other third party cookies relating to behavioural advertising, please go to www.youronlinechoices.eu.

    * any other type of cookies, you can clean the cookies through your browser settings.

Please note that refusing cookies does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the company or companies from which you opted out will no longer deliver adverts tailored to your web preferences and usage patterns, so you may see a greater number of adverts that are irrelevant to you and your preferences.

You can scroll down to see which third parties we use for deploying cookies in our website:

  | Name  
---|---  
Performance Cookies | Google Analytics  
Google Analytics Events  
Enhance Ecommerce  
Qubit  
Certona  
Functional Cookies | Responsys  
Advertising Cookies | Google Adwords  
Polyvore  
Bing  
Double Click Floodlight Counter  
Linkshare  
APPRL  
Stylight  
Channelpilot  
Social Media Cookies | Twitter  
Pinterest  
Facebook  
  8. **SECURITY**

Keeping you and your personal information secure is very important to us. We take a number of reasonable steps to try to protect the personal information that you provide, including: • using a Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) to encrypt the personal data that you send us during the order process (including any financial information such as credit or debit card details);

    * requiring you to establish a password to access your account on our Website;

not keeping details of your credit or debit card that would enable any third party to transact using that credit or debit card (such as your CCV number); and

regularly monitoring our servers and IT systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks. Unfortunately, despite this, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We cannot guarantee the security of your personal data transmitted to or through our Website, and any such transmission is at your own risk. In particular, please keep in mind that if you voluntarily disclose personal information through other means of communication than the Website in a non-protected environment (such as through email, sms, online messages) then that information can be collected and used by others outside of our or your control.

  9. **HOW LONG WILL YOU USE MY INFORMATION FOR?**

We retain the data you provide to us for as long as you have your account with us and thereafter for such period as you may have questions or a claim in relation to our services, notwithstanding any superior retention period that we may be obliged to observe in accordance with legal requirements applicable to us.

In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data as set out below.

After you have terminated your use of our services, we may store your information in an aggregated and anonymised format.

  10. **WHAT ARE MY PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

You have certain rights in relation to the personal data we hold about you, which we detail below. Some of these only apply in certain circumstances as set out in more detail below. We also set out how to exercise those rights. Please note that we will require you to verify your identity before responding to any requests to exercise your rights and that can include asking a set of security questions to ensure it is you. When you have appointed someone else to do the request on your behalf, that person and/or organization needs to show a valid power of attorney issued by you. We must respond to a request by you to exercise those rights without undue delay and at least within one month (although this may be extended by a further two months in certain circumstances). To exercise any of your rights, please contact us at [privacy@brownsfashion.com](mailto:privacy@brownsfashion.com) or by writing to Data Protection Officer, at The Bower, 4th Floor, 211 Old Street, London EC1V 9NR.

    * **_Access_.**

You have the right to know whether we process personal data about you, and if we do, to access data we hold about you and certain information about how we use it and who we share it with (including the categories of personal data we share with businesses for their direct marketing uses and the names and addresses of those businesses). Please note that in “My Account” dashboards, you can see information about you, namely your account details (such as name, email, phone number, date of birth), the addresses you use for billing and shipping, your order history and shopping preferences.

You can also request a copy of your information. If you require more than one copy of the data we hold about you, we may charge a reasonable administration fee.

We may not provide you with certain personal data if providing it would interfere with another’s rights (e.g. where providing the personal data we hold about you would reveal information about another person) or where another exemption applies.

    * **_Portability_.**

You have the right to receive a subset of the personal data we collect from you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and a right to request that we transfer such personal data to another party. The relevant subset of personal data is data that you provide us with your consent or for the purposes of performing our contract with you.

If you wish for us to transfer the personal data to another party, please ensure you detail that party and note that we can only do so where it is technically feasible. We are not responsible for the security of the personal data or its processing once received by the third party. We also may not provide you with certain data if providing it would interfere with another’s rights (e.g. where providing the personal data we hold about you would reveal information about another person or our trade secrets or intellectual property).

    * **_Correction_.**

You have the right to correct any personal data held about you that is inaccurate. You can edit your personal information in “My Account” settings. You can also request the correction by emailing us. Please note that in some cases we can ask you to explain in detail why you believe the personal data we hold about you to be inaccurate or incomplete so that we can assess whether a correction is required. Please note that whilst we assess whether the personal data we hold about you is inaccurate or incomplete, you may exercise your right to restrict our processing of the applicable data as described below.

    * **_Erasure_.**

You may request that we erase the personal data we hold about you in the certain circumstances. Please scroll below to know what those are:

      * you believe that it is no longer necessary for us to hold the personal data we hold about you;

      * we are processing the personal data we hold about you on the basis of your consent, and you wish to withdraw your consent and there is no other ground under which we can process the personal data;

      * we are processing the personal data we hold about you on the basis of our legitimate interest and you object to such processing. Please provide us with detail as to your reasoning so that we can assess whether there is an overriding interest for us to retain such personal data;

      * you no longer wish us to use the personal data we hold about you in order to send you promotions and special offers;

      * you believe the personal data we hold about you is being unlawfully processed by us.

Also note that you may exercise your right to restrict our processing the data whilst we consider your request as described below.

Please provide as much detail as possible on your reasons for the request to assist us in determining whether you have a valid basis for erasure. Please note, however, that we may retain the personal data if there are valid grounds under law for us to do so (e.g., for the defence of legal claims or freedom of expression) but we will let you know if that is the case.

Where you have requested that we erase data that we have made public and there are grounds for erasure, we will use reasonable steps try to tell others that are displaying the data or providing links to the data to erase the data too.

    * **_Restriction of Processing to Storage Only_.**

You have a right to require us to stop processing the personal data we hold about you other than for storage purposes in certain circumstances. Please note, however, that if we stop processing the personal data, we may use it again if there are valid grounds under data protection law for us to do so (e.g. for the defence of legal claims or for another’s protection)

Please scroll below to know the cases where you may request we stop processing and just store the personal data we hold about you.

      * you believe the personal data is not accurate for the period it takes for us to verify your claim;

      * we wish to erase the personal data as the processing we are doing is unlawful but you want us to retain the personal data for storage but not further process it;

      * we wish to erase the personal data as it is no longer necessary for our purposes but you require it to be stored for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; or

      * you have objected to us processing personal data we hold about you on the basis of our legitimate interest and you wish us to stop processing the personal data whilst we determine whether there is an overriding interest in us retaining such personal data.

    * **_Objection_.**

At any time you have the right to object to our processing of data about you in order to send you promotions and special offers, including where we build profiles for such purposes and we will stop processing the data for that purpose. You can do so by changing your marketing preferences at “My Account” or by ticking “unsubscribe” at the bottom of each marketing email we send you. Please note that you will still receive emails related with the orders you make through our Website or updates to our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy.

You also have the right to object to our processing of data about you and we will consider your request in other circumstances as detailed below:

      * we are processing the data we hold about you (including where the processing is profiling) on the basis of our or a third party’s legitimate interest and you object to such processing. Please provide us with detail as to your reasoning so that we can assess whether there is a compelling overriding interest in us continuing to process such data or we need to process it in relation to legal claims. Also note that you may exercise your right to request that we stop processing the data whilst we make the assessment on an overriding interest;

**Withdrawal of Consent:** You can withdraw your consent at any time by changing your marketing preferences in “My Account” or by unsubscribing at the bottom of each email received or by writing emailing us as set out below.

  11. **COMPLAINTS**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:;

    * by emailing us at [privacy@brownsfashion.com](mailto:privacy@brownsfashion.com); or

    * by writing to the Data Protection Officer, at The Bower, 4th Floor, 211 Old Street, London EC1V 9NR.

This is without prejudice to your right to launch a claim with the Information Commissioner’s Office (www.ico.org.uk) or the data protection supervisory authority in the EU country in which you live or work where you think we have infringed data protection laws.”

  12. **UPDATES TO THIS POLICY**

Any changes we may make to this Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. Please check back regularly to keep informed of updates or changes to this Privacy Policy.

##### Job Applicant Privacy Notice 

As part of any recruitment process, Browns (South Molton Street) Limited collects and processes personal data relating to job applicants. The organisation is committed to being transparent about how it collects and uses that data and to meeting its data protection obligations. 

Browns (South Molton Street) Limited, registered at The Bower, 4th Floor, 211 Old Street, London EC1V 9NR, United Kingdom (“we”, “us” or “our”) are the data controller for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR"). We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy sets out the basis on which we process any personal data that you provide to us and other data we receive from you or third parties (such as referees) in connection with your job application.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your data and how we will treat it. By sending us an email submitting your application you acknowledge and agree to the practices described in this policy.

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, you can contact us at [privacy@brownsfashion.com](mailto:privacy@brownsfashion.com).

**What information do we collect?**

Browns (South Molton Street) Limited collects a range of information about you. This includes: 

  * your name, address and contact details, including email address and telephone number; 
  * details of your qualifications, skills, experience and employment history; 
  * information about your current level of remuneration, including benefit entitlements; 
  * with your consent, whether or not you have a disability for which the organisation needs to make reasonable adjustments during the recruitment process; and 
  * information about your entitlement to work in the UK. 

Browns (South Molton Street) Limited may collect this information in a variety of ways. For example, data might be contained in CVs or resumes, obtained from your passport or other identity documents, or collected through interviews or other forms of assessment. 

We may also collect personal data about you from third parties, such as references supplied by former employers, or recruitment agencies. We can also seek information from third parties, including once a job offer to you has been made and will inform you that we are doing so. 

Data will be stored in a range of different places, including on your application record, in HR management systems and on other IT systems (including email). 

**Why does Browns (South Molton Street) Limited process personal data?**

We use your information to perform a contract with you, namely through:

  * identify and evaluate you for employment positions;
  * determine and validate your qualifications for employment;
  * conduct background checks including, to the extent permitted under applicable law (including checking references and qualifications).
  * if you are a successful candidate, create an employment record;

These uses of your information are needed to enter into a contract with you. 

In some cases, we need to process data to ensure that we are complying with our legal obligations. For example, it is mandatory to check a successful applicant's eligibility to work in the UK before employment starts. 

Browns (South Molton Street) Limited has a legitimate interest in processing personal data during the recruitment process and for keeping records of the process. Processing data from job applicants allows us to manage the recruitment process, assess and confirm a candidate's suitability for employment and decide to whom to offer a job. We may also need to process data from job applicants to respond to and defend against legal claims. 

With your consent, Browns (South Molton Street) Limited may process special categories of data, such as information about ethnic origin, sexual orientation or religion or belief, to monitor recruitment statistics, which will be kept in an anonymized format. Your application will not be prejudiced if you decide not to disclose this information. We may also collect information about whether or not applicants are disabled to make reasonable adjustments for candidates who have a disability. We process such information to carry out our obligations and exercise specific rights in relation to employment

If your application is unsuccessful, Browns (South Molton Street) Limited may keep your personal data on file in case there are future employment opportunities for which you may be suited. We will ask for your consent before it keeps your data for this purpose and you are free to withdraw your consent at any time. 

**Who do you share my data with?**

Your information may be shared internally for the purposes of the recruitment exercise. This includes members of the People and Talent team, interviewers involved in the recruitment process, managers in the business area with a vacancy and IT staff if access to the data is necessary for the performance of their roles. 

We will share your data with third parties which can be your former employers to obtain references for you, as well as employment background check providers to obtain necessary background checks.

Browns (South Molton Street) is part of a larger family of companies in different parts of the world, the Farfetch Group. As such, we can share your information with Farfetch UK Limited, for the purposes of global headcount monitoring and forecast. 

**How does Browns (South Molton Street) Limited protect data?**

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we take the security of your data seriously and we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted through email; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard your personal data against loss, theft and unauthorised use, access or modification 

**For how long does Browns (South Molton Street) Limited keep data?**

If your application for employment is unsuccessful, the organisation will hold your data on file for 6 (six) months after the end of the relevant recruitment process. If you give us your consent to allow us to keep your personal data on file, we will hold your data on file for a further 6 (six) months for consideration for future employment opportunities. At the end of that period, or once you withdraw your consent, your data is deleted or destroyed. You will be asked when you submit your CV whether you give us consent to hold your details for the full 12 months in order to be considered for other positions or not. 

If your application for employment is successful, personal data gathered during the recruitment process will be transferred to your Human Resources file (electronic and paper based) and retained during your employment. The periods for which your data will be held will be provided to you in a new privacy notice. 

**Your rights**

As a data subject, you have a number of rights. You can: 

  * access and obtain a copy of your data on request; 
  * require the organisation to change incorrect or incomplete data; 
  * require the organisation to delete or stop processing your data, for example where the data is no longer necessary for the purposes of processing; and 
  * object to the processing of your data where Browns (South Molton Street) Limited is relying on its legitimate interests as the legal ground for processing. 
  * If you have provided consent for the processing of your data you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time which will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent was withdrawn.

If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact [privacy@brownsfashion.com](mailto:privacy@brownsfashion.com). We must respond to a request by you to exercise those rights without undue delay and at least within one (1) month (although this may be extended by a further two (2) months in certain circumstances) 

If you believe that the organisation has not complied with your data protection rights, you can complain to the Information Commissioner Officer (ICO) 

**Changes**

We will post any future changes to this policy on this page. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to this policy. 

**Contact**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this policy are welcomed and should be addressed to Farfetch Group Data Protection Officer at the following email: address privacy@brownsfashion.com

##### Browns East: Marketing Collection Form Privacy Notice

We are Browns (South Molton Street) Limited (“Browns”, “we”, “us” or “our”) and we are committed to protecting our customers’ privacy. You have provided us with certain personal information about yourself during your recent visit to our Browns East boutique, which potentially includes your name, email address home address, gender, phone number and date of birth. This privacy notice sets out how we use this information and who it may be shared with.

We are a company registered in England and Wales (Company No. 06887728), with its registered office located at The Bower, 4th Floor 211 Old Street, London, EC1V 9NR, United Kingdom. Our ICO registration number is ZA098442 (the ICO is the UK’s data protection regulator) and you can access its ICO notification [here](https://ico.org.uk/ESDWebPages/Entry/ZA098442).

  1. **WHAT DO YOU USE MY INFORMATION FOR?**

To provide you services and the Website, including to allow you to order and receive products using our Website, administer your account and to optimise your experience we need to use the information that we collect in a number of different ways.

We also use the information for marketing and advertising purposes. Where you have told us you would like to receive marketing communications or when you have made a purchase using our services, we and our partner boutiques will use your personal information (including your name, email address and address) to occasionally send you updates, news, and offers via email, post, or other forms of media. We may use your information (including supplemental information received from partners that we append to our existing customer information as described below), to tailor these messages to you. You may unsubscribe from email marketing communications by modifying your preferences in your account’s profile management section, or by following the opt out instructions in the promotional emails we send you.

We use third-party service providers to serve advertisements most relevant to you across your different devices and on our own and others’ websites and mobile applications. In addition to the information about your visits to our website or usage of our mobile application, our service providers may also use the information about your interactions with other websites or applications to target advertisements for products available from Browns. For information about opting out of targeted advertising and controlling the use of cookies, please see the cookies section of this Privacy Policy.

We also carry out research, analysis, and surveys on your use of our Website, and views. We keep tracking of your spend on our Website to see if you can benefit from our exclusive loyalty programs as the VIC customer program and Access. Finally we use your information to confirm your identity and perform credit checks or anti-fraud checks, in order to ensure your, and our, financial security.

Please note that we do not sell your information without your consent (whether your name, address, emails address, financial information, or otherwise) to any third party.

Please scroll down to find out the detailed purposes for which we collect your information, what specific information is collected and the legal basis for which we purpose that data.

Processing Purpose | Types of Data | Legal Basis  
---|---|---  
To register and manage your account in our Website | Name, email, password and other additional details you may wish to add in your account, like phone number addresses and gender. | Performance of a Contract with you  
To fulfil the orders you make through our website | Name, addresses, phone number, Order details, like the products you are buying, the size and price. | Performance of a Contract with you  
To collect payment from you | Payment information, which comprises the credit/debit card’s number, holder’s name and CCV – we do not store them and only transfer them to our authorized payment providers. | Performance of a Contract with you  
To provide you with our customer services (including helping you to solve any issue you have with our services, updating you about any change to our terms of service, or contacting you to know how was your experience with us) | Name, email, password and addresses and your contact history with us (including phone records of our conversations) | Contract and legitimate interests in retaining you as a customer  
To monitor the quality of our customer services | Name, email, password and addresses and your contact history with us | Legitimate interests in running our business  
To administer, maintain and optimise our Website and our services | Device information (such as your device IP address and device type), Cookie identifiers and browsing information | Legitimate interests in running our business  
To perform fraud and credit checks and if we can do business with you | Name; email; addresses; credit/debit card details; browsing history; purchase history; date of birth; gender; device information (such as IP address and device type), any national identifiers (like driver’s license or ID cards) and any publicly available information (like social media profiles or news) | Legitimate interests to protect Browns and its customers from fraudulent activities and compliance with a legal obligation  
To send you marketing communications and personalised offers | Name; Email; Phone Number; Addresses; Date of Birth;  
Purchase history; Browsing history and behaviour; Device information;  
Shopping preferences; Cookie identifiers; Internal identifiers; Country | Legitimate interests to electronic direct marketing of similar products and services to that which you have acquired using our Website or, when such is not applicable, your Consent.  
Analysis of your behaviour and purchases in our Website | Name; Email; Phone Number; Addresses; Date of Birth; Purchase history; Browsing history and behaviour; Device Information;  
Shopping preferences; Nickname; Cookie identifiers; Internal identifiers; Country; Spent tier level and Wealth. | Legitimate interests in running our business and improve our Website and your experience  
Carry on enquiries and surveys on your use of our website and views | Email; Device information, demographic information (including gender, country of residence and household income) and content of survey responses | Legitimate interests in running our business and improve our Website and your experience.  
Advertising and retarget advertising | Email; Cookie Identifiers; Device Information; | Legitimate Interests in running our business  
  2. **WHO DO YOU SHARE MY INFORMATION WITH?**

To provide the Website and our services, we work with a number of carefully selected third parties. To do this, we may share your information with these third parties in the following limited circumstances:

    * **Group companies for business purposes:** Browns (South Molton Street) Limited is part of a larger family of companies in different parts of the world. Our group of companies, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company, and that company’s subsidiaries as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006, includes Browns (South Molton Street) Limited, Fashion Concierge UK Limited, Farfetch Portugal – Unipessoal, Lda., Farfetch.com Limited, Farfetch.com US LLC., Farfetch.com Brasil Servicos LTDA, Farfetch Japan Co Ltd and Farfetch (Shanghai) E-Commerce Co. Ltd (the “Farfetch Group”). We may share your personal information in order to operate our business and provide the Website and services. Rest assured, their use of information is consistent with this Privacy Policy;

    * **Third party service providers for business purposes:** We have subcontracted the operation of certain aspects of the Site to Black & White, a trading division of Farfetch UK Limited (company number 06400760, VAT number GB 204 0769 35). Services provided or procured by Farfetch include, but are not limited to, payment processing, customer service, hosting and delivery logistics

    * **advertisers for marketing purposes:** we can provide your information to our advertising and social media partners (including Facebook and Twitter, where you choose) where they require the data to select and serve relevant adverts about our products and services to you and others;

    * **third parties where we are considering a corporate transaction:** the Farfetch Group is always looking for new opportunities and directions in which to grow, and that may take into account Browns. This means sometimes we may consider corporate transactions such as merger, acquisitions, reorganisations, asset sale, or similar. In these instances, we may transfer your information to enable the assessment and undertaking of that transaction. If we buy or sell any business or assets, your personal information may be one of the assets that are transferred;

    * **to comply with legal requests:** on occasion we may be required to liaise with various regulators and law enforcement agencies in a number of different countries, whether as a result of law, a court order, or another legal process. Although we dispute requests wherever suitable, in some cases we may have to share your information with the regulators or law enforcement agencies. Where we consider it appropriate, and provided we are not prohibited from doing so by law or court order, we will attempt to notify you of these legal demands; and

    * **aggregated information with third parties:** we may aggregate your information with the information of other customers, creating a dataset of information about the usage of our Website, purchase of products, and other general, grouped information about our customers on the basis of our legitimate interest to understand the usage of our service and demand for our product. Although this dataset is aggregated and anonymised, meaning it cannot identify you as an individual, it provides a valuable insight into the use of our Website and we may therefore share it with select third parties. These parties may include providers of plugins or similar technologies to help measure traffic, our partner boutiques and other providers to allow them to better stock products, and our investors. Please note that we do not share your information with any third party advertisers or networks for the provision of third party advertising on our Website.

**3\. CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:;

  * by emailing us at [privacy@farfetch.com](mailto:privacy@farfetch.com); or

  * by writing to the Data Protection Officer, at The Bower, 4th Floor, 211 Old Street, London EC1V 9NR.

This is without prejudice to your right to launch a claim with the Information Commissioner’s Office (www.ico.org.uk) or the data protection supervisory authority in the EU country in which you live or work where you think we have infringed data protection laws.”

**4\. UPDATES TO THIS POLICY**

Any changes we may make to this Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. Please check back regularly to keep informed of updates or changes to this Privacy Policy.
